<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>CYBERTEC Migrator on CYBERTEC Migrator Documentation</title><link>https://cybertec-postgresql.github.io/cybertec_migrator/</link><description>Recent content in CYBERTEC Migrator on CYBERTEC Migrator Documentation</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 09:12:43 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cybertec-postgresql.github.io/cybertec_migrator/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Requirements</title><link>https://cybertec-postgresql.github.io/cybertec_migrator/getting-started/requirements/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 15:27:44 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://cybertec-postgresql.github.io/cybertec_migrator/getting-started/requirements/</guid><description>CYBERTEC Migrator is distributed as a set of container images that are managed with the help of Docker Compose.
docker docker compose (&amp;gt;= 2.0.0) git (&amp;gt;= 2.20.1) bash (&amp;gt;= 4.0)</description></item><item><title>Installation</title><link>https://cybertec-postgresql.github.io/cybertec_migrator/getting-started/installation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 15:28:36 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://cybertec-postgresql.github.io/cybertec_migrator/getting-started/installation/</guid><description>The CYBERTEC Migrator images can be obtained via two channels
Online installation via container registry Offline installation for environments in which networking restrictions are imposed The Migrator Trial Edition is only available as an offline installation package. It is exclusively intended for private or testing purposes, unless explicit authorization is obtained. Online The docker images are available on the Docker Hub container image registry.
Please get in touch with us if your account has not been granted access to the respective images.</description></item><item><title>Usage</title><link>https://cybertec-postgresql.github.io/cybertec_migrator/getting-started/usage/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 15:28:36 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://cybertec-postgresql.github.io/cybertec_migrator/getting-started/usage/</guid><description>Use your web browser to access the Migrator on the URL shown in the terminal with ./migrator up. In our example it would be https://localhost.
The configuration provided with this repository starts the CYBERTEC Migrator on the standard HTTPS port. The EXTERNAL_HTTP_PORT variable in the .env file (generated by ./migrator configure) controls the choice of port on which the Migrator is served.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t have access to an Oracle or PostgreSQL database to test the Migrator, check out our Migrator demo database environment.</description></item><item><title>Upgrade</title><link>https://cybertec-postgresql.github.io/cybertec_migrator/getting-started/upgrade/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 15:28:36 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://cybertec-postgresql.github.io/cybertec_migrator/getting-started/upgrade/</guid><description>Akin to the installation, the upgrade may be done online or offline.
Upgrades between different editions may be done at will, no data will be lost.
Running migrations will be interrupted by applying upgrades. Online Update release information Upgrade to newest version Apply upgrade ./migrator update ./migrator upgrade ./migrator up Offline Update release information Upgrade to version bundled in archive Apply upgrade ./migrator update --archive cybertec_migrator-edition-vX.Y.Z.tar.gz ./migrator upgrade --archive cybertec_migrator-edition-vX.Y.Z.tar.gz .</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://cybertec-postgresql.github.io/cybertec_migrator/help/faq/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 14:26:51 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cybertec-postgresql.github.io/cybertec_migrator/help/faq/</guid><description>Installation and Configuration How do I configure TCPS for Oracle databases? How do I generate a self-signed certificate How do I install an existing certificate? How do I set environment variables Troubleshooting ORA-12637: Packet receive failed while verifying source credentials Installation and Configuration How do I configure TCPS for Oracle databases? Install sqlnet.ora and tnsnames.ora from the template files.
➜ TNS_ADMIN=./volumes/core/config/oracle/network/admin ➜ cp &amp;#34;$TNS_ADMIN/templates&amp;#34;/*.ora &amp;#34;$TNS_ADMIN/&amp;#34; Add the net service name of the secure connection to the volumes/core/config/oracle/network/admin/tnsnames.</description></item><item><title>Supported Features</title><link>https://cybertec-postgresql.github.io/cybertec_migrator/features/oracle/supported-features/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 09:12:43 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://cybertec-postgresql.github.io/cybertec_migrator/features/oracle/supported-features/</guid><description>Database Object Types CREATE Comment DATABASE LINK ✅ visible, use PostgreSQL [Foreign Data Wrapper] DIRECTORY ❌ FUNCTION ✅ code needs to be translated manually INDEX ✅ MATERIALIZED VIEW ✅ PACKAGE ✅ package code visible, code needs to be translated manually PROCEDURE ✅ code needs to be translated manually SCHEMA ✅ SEQUENCE ✅ SYNONYMS ✅ visible, have to be migrated manually TABLE ✅ partitions (hash, list, range) supported TRIGGER ✅ TYPE ✅ USER ❌ VIEW ✅ Built-In Data Types Detailed information about Oracle built-in data types may be found in the Oracle SQL Language Reference.</description></item><item><title>Code Transpilation</title><link>https://cybertec-postgresql.github.io/cybertec_migrator/features/code-transpilation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2024 09:11:10 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://cybertec-postgresql.github.io/cybertec_migrator/features/code-transpilation/</guid><description>The CYBERTEC Migrator is able to parse, analyze and transpile certain PL/SQL constructs to PL/pgSQL automatically. Each supported construct is represented by a corresponding rule.
This feature-set is under ongoing development, adding new rules wherever possible. If you have a suggestion for a new rule, please open a feature request.
CYAR-0001: AddParamlistParentheses Example CYAR-0002: ReplacePrologue Example CYAR-0003: ReplaceEpilogue Example CYAR-0004: FixTrunc CYAR-0005: ReplaceSysdate Example CYAR-0006: ReplaceNvl Example CYAR-0007: RemoveEditionable Example CYAR-0008: ReplaceNvl2 Example CYAR-0001: AddParamlistParentheses In Oracle, a procedure without parameters may omit parentheses in its definition, whereas PostgreSQL always requires them.</description></item><item><title>EULA</title><link>https://cybertec-postgresql.github.io/cybertec_migrator/license/eula/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 14:26:51 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cybertec-postgresql.github.io/cybertec_migrator/license/eula/</guid><description>End-User License Agreement Last updated: 02.05.2022
This End-User License Agreement (referred to as the &amp;ldquo;EULA&amp;rdquo;) is a legally binding agreement between you, the Licensee, an individual customer or entity, and the CYBERTEC PostgreSQL International GmbH, the company, and the author of CYBERTEC MIGRATOR, the Software, which may include associated media, printed materials, and online or electronic documentation. This Agreement is a legally binding contract that includes terms that limit your legal rights and Licensors&amp;rsquo; liability to you, and shall govern all access to and use of this Software.</description></item></channel></rss>