<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Getting Started on CYBERTEC Migrator</title><link>https://cybertec-migrator.github.io/cybertec-migrator/getting-started/</link><description>Recent content in Getting Started on CYBERTEC Migrator</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 15:28:36 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cybertec-migrator.github.io/cybertec-migrator/getting-started/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Requirements</title><link>https://cybertec-migrator.github.io/cybertec-migrator/getting-started/requirements/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 15:27:44 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://cybertec-migrator.github.io/cybertec-migrator/getting-started/requirements/</guid><description>CYBERTEC Migrator is distributed as a set of container images that are managed with the help of Docker Compose.
docker docker compose (&amp;gt;= 2.0.0) git (&amp;gt;= 2.20.1) bash (&amp;gt;= 4.0)</description></item><item><title>Installation</title><link>https://cybertec-migrator.github.io/cybertec-migrator/getting-started/installation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 15:28:36 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://cybertec-migrator.github.io/cybertec-migrator/getting-started/installation/</guid><description>The CYBERTEC Migrator images can be obtained via two channels
Online installation via container registry Offline installation for environments in which networking restrictions are imposed The Migrator Trial Edition is only available as an offline installation package. It is exclusively intended for private or testing purposes, unless explicit authorization is obtained. Online The docker images are available on the Docker Hub container image registry.
Please get in touch with us if your account has not been granted access to the respective images.</description></item><item><title>Usage</title><link>https://cybertec-migrator.github.io/cybertec-migrator/getting-started/usage/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 15:28:36 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://cybertec-migrator.github.io/cybertec-migrator/getting-started/usage/</guid><description>Use your web browser to access the Migrator on the URL shown in the terminal with ./migrator up. In our example it would be https://localhost.
The configuration provided with this repository starts the CYBERTEC Migrator on the standard HTTPS port. The EXTERNAL_HTTP_PORT variable in the .env file (generated by ./migrator configure) controls the choice of port on which the Migrator is served.
If you don&amp;rsquo;t have access to an Oracle or PostgreSQL database to test the Migrator, check out our Migrator demo database environment.</description></item><item><title>Upgrade</title><link>https://cybertec-migrator.github.io/cybertec-migrator/getting-started/upgrade/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jul 2024 15:28:36 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://cybertec-migrator.github.io/cybertec-migrator/getting-started/upgrade/</guid><description>Akin to the installation, the upgrade may be done online or offline.
Upgrades between different editions may be done at will, no data will be lost.
Running migrations will be interrupted by applying upgrades. Online Update release information Upgrade to newest version Apply upgrade ./migrator update ./migrator upgrade ./migrator up Offline Update release information Upgrade to version bundled in archive Apply upgrade ./migrator update --archive cybertec_migrator-edition-vX.Y.Z.tar.gz ./migrator upgrade --archive cybertec_migrator-edition-vX.Y.Z.tar.gz .</description></item></channel></rss>